<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eyal Yavor</title>
    <link>https://yulkes.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eyal Yavor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:35:20 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yulkes.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why There&#39;s Nothing Here (Yet)</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/posts/why-theres-nothing-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:35:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/posts/why-theres-nothing-here/</guid>
      <description>To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing my writing nowadays on my upcoming book: Hacking the Home Assignment, a guide for Junior Developers who want a better shot at passing the new age of technical interviews.
In the past I&amp;rsquo;ve written all over the place, in Medium, in our company&amp;rsquo;s internal blog, and even a personal blog.
Hopefully in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll find content worthy of this blog&amp;rsquo;s pages, and not only as part of the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking the Home Assignment</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/talks/hackingthehomeassignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/talks/hackingthehomeassignment/</guid>
      <description>Workshop based on my book in progress.
Helping junior developers solve home assignments better: Work like professionals, improve their odds, and receive higher offers.
Workshop for Junior Developers Home assignments are here to stay as they offer less biased views and are more focused on the quality of your work.
Unfortunately, if you’re a Junior Developer, the quality of work is usually what stands out. Your projects won’t look like what a professional reviewer is used to: They may be messy, half-working, or lacking documentation and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/posts/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 22:15:46 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/posts/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Hello!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Engineering in the Worst Work Environment</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/talks/greatengineeringworstworkenvironment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/talks/greatengineeringworstworkenvironment/</guid>
      <description>Imagine the worst possible engineering work environment: Strict dress code, fast employee turnaround with median age of 19, people gone for 2 weeks in the middle of a project, requirements and priorities that change monthly. Oh, and there&amp;rsquo;s no internet access.
Welcome to the Israeli Intelligence Unit, which despite its limitations produces world-class results.
Learn how all these workplace disadvantages turned to the unit&amp;rsquo;s advantage, and what lessons you can take from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How We Ditched Our Apps and Built a Robot Instead</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/talks/howweditchedourapps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 13:45:10 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/talks/howweditchedourapps/</guid>
      <description>My partners and I cofounded Meekan, a calendar scheduling platform, raised funding, and went the standard way - develop iOS, Android and Outlook apps for it.
A year later we had 3 apps, lots of code, not much money and and very few users.
As one last shot, we tried meeting our users where they were - in an up-and-coming work tool called Slack. Only problem - The only integration we could write there was a chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Your Chatbot Sucks</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/talks/whyyourchatbotsucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 13:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/talks/whyyourchatbotsucks/</guid>
      <description>If you jumped on the chatbot-wagon in the past year, that&amp;rsquo;s nice, but you can probably do a lot better. This talk outlines tips &amp;amp; tricks to make your bot more useful, intuitive, smarter, and fun to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Your Chatbot With Redis</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/talks/scalingyourchatbotwithredis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 13:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/talks/scalingyourchatbotwithredis/</guid>
      <description>Short talk on how Meekan uses Redis to implement a fast-responding and quickly-improving chatbot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yulkes.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yulkes.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey There!
I&amp;rsquo;m Eyal, a.k.a. yulkes, a software developer and an engineering lead. Short history: Served in the Israeli Intelligence Unit as a software developer, joined IdMlogic as an Identity Management consultant for large enterprises, co-founded Meekan which was acquired by Doodle, where I was a dev lead of the Israeli office.
I talk often, but sometimes I also do public speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>